<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-11-23T01:04:48+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Harsh Trivedi</title><author><name>Harsh Trivedi</name></author><entry><title type="html">A day with some boring guests</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/A-boring-day-with-some-guests" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A day with some boring guests" /><published>2018-09-20T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-09-20T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/A-boring-day-with-some-guests</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/A-boring-day-with-some-guests">&lt;center&gt;&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:1rem;padding: 0.25vmax;max-width:82.5vmax;background-color:#f2415e;text-transform: uppercase; color:#ffffff;&quot;&gt;Before starting off with the main story, let me tell you one important thing, if you are a boring guest, then please don't read this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Boring guests, they teach us many things, like how things work, how unfair life is, how to be patient, and how to deal with some boring people when they actually don’t know how boring they are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now let me start off with the story, the day before yesterday I was sitting in my room trying to troubleshoot some errors in one of my code, some random old guests came to meet my family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They were not a disturbing element for me until they called my name as they were busy talking with my parents, but suddenly they called me and started asking annoying questions about my studies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not that good in studies, so obviously the question they asked, troubled me a bit, but I managed to give them a meaningful answer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was trying to escape the spot but then those boring people asked me to sit and chat with them, but back in my mind, I was thinking about the solution to the error in my code that was bothering me from past 30 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I finally got the solution to my error but those slow guests were stuck in their position and were not at all ready to leave (I know I sound a bit rude at this point, but if you would’ve experienced those type of boring guests, you would’ve got bored too. 😛)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, after wasting my 1 hour in some boring chit-chat with those boring fellows, I got the chance to fix my problem and after that, the day ended on a lighter note.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;p style=&quot;max-width:25rem;text-align:center;background-color:#999fff;color:#ffffff;padding:0.25vmax;font-size:1rem;&quot;&gt;&lt;a style=&quot;color:#ffffff;&quot; href=&quot;https://www.freepik.com/free-vector/bored-student_787766.htm&quot;&gt;Vector Used in Post Image&lt;/a&gt; by &lt;b&gt;Freepik&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/center&gt;</content><author><name>Harsh Trivedi</name></author><summary type="html">Before starting off with the main story, let me tell you one important thing, if you are a boring guest, then please don't read this.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://i.imgur.com/Hs9WzIQ.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Hello World</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/Hello-World" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hello World" /><published>2018-09-02T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-09-02T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/Hello-World</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/Hello-World">&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone, I am &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/harsh98trivedi&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Harsh Trivedi&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a &lt;strong&gt;19&lt;/strong&gt;-year-old guy, who loves each and every aspect of &lt;em&gt;Technology&lt;/em&gt;. My life started in a lovely city, &lt;strong&gt;Kanpur&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;(formerly Cawnpore)&lt;/em&gt;,  the 11th most populous urban city located in the central part of &lt;strong&gt;Uttar Pradesh, India&lt;/strong&gt;. I love Graphic Designing, Web Development, Video Editing, Travelling, Learning new things and Making new friends with similar interest and mindset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Computer&lt;/em&gt;, is my most favorite subject since childhood, and has completely changed the way I think and understand things, the best part about a computer is the learning experience, whether you are designing some stuff, editing a video or programming an app, if you are doing all that with a goal in mind and with full dedication, you’ll surely learn how things work and how you need to work with them or tweak them in your own possible way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am starting this &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jekyll&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; based blog to share my thoughts, experiences, knowledge, and much more, I will share most of my social activities now and then, also I will be sharing some apps, websites, and tools that I have made or I am using for making my tech activities easy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I currently live in Kanpur, where people are mostly boring, but exceptions are always there so I found &lt;a href=&quot;https://kanpurfoss.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KanpurFOSS Community&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, where we do &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.meetup.com/WordPress-Kanpur&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;meetups&lt;/a&gt;, workshops, and a &lt;a href=&quot;https://kanpur.wordcamp.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;WordCamp&lt;/a&gt; every year, I would like to thank KanpurFOSS Community for sharing an awesome tech experience here, in Kanpur.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to know more &lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/#about-section&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;about&lt;/a&gt; me, you can simply &lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/#contact-section&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;contact&lt;/a&gt; me using different social media platforms mentioned in the navbar.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will also be sharing some of the Tweets, Facebook Posts, Instagram photos and YouTube videos using a simple embed or using some sort of API.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;
&lt;img id=&quot;hello-world-harsh-img&quot; width=&quot;250vmax&quot; style=&quot;border-radius:25rem;&quot; src=&quot;https://www.gravatar.com/avatar/0d73468bd0b0258eb61d9358352ecb7b?s=720&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;</content><author><name>Harsh Trivedi</name></author><summary type="html">Hello everyone, I am Harsh Trivedi, a 19-year-old guy, who loves each and every aspect of Technology. My life started in a lovely city, Kanpur (formerly Cawnpore), the 11th most populous urban city located in the central part of Uttar Pradesh, India. I love Graphic Designing, Web Development, Video Editing, Travelling, Learning new things and Making new friends with similar interest and mindset.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://i.imgur.com/8aFFy4S.jpg" /></entry></feed>